myhelphub.com 2009-04-18

# myHelpHub.com - Online support for the WCCL Network

**Our Commitment To Privacy**

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.

****

**The Information We Collect**

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the various websites owned by the WCCL Network. On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are: 

Name   
E-mail address  
Products you wish to order  

Your address is never taken, nor are your credit card details. These items are handled by the relevant payments processor, such as SWREG or PayPal.

On some pages, you can submit information about other people. For example, if you order a gift online and want it sent directly to the recipient, you will need to submit the recipient's address. In this circumstance, the types of personal information collected are: 

Name of recipient  
E-mail address of recipient

****

**The Way We Use Information**

We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order. 

We use the information you provide about someone else when placing an order only to ship the product and to confirm delivery. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order. 

We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties. 

You can register with our website if you would like to receive our various newsletters, as well as updates on new products and services. Information you submit on our website will not be used for this purpose unless you fill out the registration form and confirm your address by verified double opt-in. Newsletters are typically sent out once a week. 

We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals. 

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses. 

**Our Commitment To Data Security**

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

**Our Commitment To Children's Privacy**

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13. 

**How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information**

You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by writing to us and making an official request. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information. 

You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error. 

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. 

If you wish to unsubscribe from a newsletter you are receiving, or a mailing list you have joined, you can do so by clicking the unsubscribe link at the bottom of the message.

**How To Unsubscribe from Newsletters**

If you are receiving a newsletter from us, you can unsubscribe by clicking on the link at the bottom of every single message we send out.

If you wish to stop receiving peer-initiated and other messages from us, you can add yourself to our global unsubscribe list at [ http://www.myhelphub.com/start/global.aspx](http://www.myhelphub.com/start/global.aspx). Please note that adding yourself to this list is irreversible.

**How To Contact Us**

Should you have other questions or concerns about this privacy policy, please contact us online at <http://www.myhelphub.com/start/contact.aspx>

You can also mail us at: WCCL Network, RCM #28011, 14525 SW Millikan Way, Beaverton, Oregon, 97005-2343, United States. 

For instructions on contacting our support team by telephone, please dial (US) 641-715-3900, extension 30309#.

**Copyright Warning**

The unauthorized reproduction or distribution of our copyrighted work is illegal. Criminal copyright infringement, including infringement without monetary gain, is investigated by the FBI and is punishable by up to 5 years in federal prison and a fine of $250,000.
